MAXIMILIANO ESPECHE

System Engineer - Certified Scrum Master



DETAILS

PROFILE

Tucumán Argentina +5493813032415 maximilianoespeche@gmail.com Through several experiences, I have developed what I believe to be my greatest strength: the ability to learn quickly and independently, resulting in tangible accomplishments.

As a result, I have gained expertise in a variety of areas, including Agile methodologies, Scrum framework, iOS, Android, web development, Windows development, IT, Genexus, design (Adobe Products), and architecture (Autocad, SketchUp), among manji,other programs that I have learned over the past 10 years to successfully execute projects under my leadership.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Tucuman State Administration - Argentina

Since 2017 - Today Tucumán, Argentina Scrum Master of the project Tucuman Mascotas App, Public pets and street animals, care and registry. Working as only responsible for the project. Working with agile technologies and more than 10 people in charge.

EME Solutions AR

Since 2017 - Today Tucumán, Argentina Agile Coach, Scrum Master & Software Developer services - Since I created this company I have been walking through all the stages that work has required to satisfy many kinds of clients.

Starting as a full time developer and today in charge of the whole team.

Global Gallery NFT

Since 2022 - Today Tucumán, Argentina

Started as a personal project, today we are a community where I'm in charge of a team.

Working with artist, graphic designers and crypto specialist.

FREELANCER DEVELOPER

WORKING WITH THE FOLLOWING COSTUMERS:

Punto Damia

Since 2017 - Today, Tucumán, Argentina

I had been part of the creation of this company, designing many of the process and in charge of the whole software developer team. Consultant, Scrum Master and Manager System Department

Soler Group: 9 bars and restaurants

Since 2017 - Today Tucumán, Argentina

Since 2017 - Today

Tucumán, Argentina

During the beginning of this project, I was focused on developing an adaptive platform to manage 9 points of sales. Today, I'm in charge of receiving the tickets of the users, more than 50 persons switching turns, analyzing those tickets and design and assigning the solutions.

Since 2017 - until 2023 Tucumán, Argentina

Picon Store

- -Consultant
- -Project manager and Full-stack Developer

June 2019 Tucumán, Argentina

New Holland dealer

IT, wiring structure and server setup



EDUCATION

December 2017 Tucumán, Argentina Universidad Tecnológica Nacional - Facultad Regional de Tucumán

Degree: Information System Engineer Description: Graduated with 8.44 average

Scrum Alliance

June 2023

Degree: Certified Scrum Master



SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE

Fast learning
Agile methodologies - Advanced level
Scrum Framework - Advanced level
Kanban Framework - Basic knowledge

Genexus - Certified Senior Genexus Developer
Git - Advanced level
JS - Advanced level
HTML - Advanced level
ReactJS Framework - Advanced level
CSS - Intermediate level
ISO - Intermediate level
SQL - Intermediate level
Adobe Package - Intermediate level
Java - Basic knowledge
AWS Services - Basic knowledge

Spanish - Native Speaker English - Intermediate level, professional competency